Anointing is the power of God; anointing is in the house.
I say, anointing is in the house.
All you need to do is to put your demand by faith on the anointing.
You are a faith man; you are a faith woman.
The right hand of God is power.
Listen once again.
Grudge has created a room for depression.
Whatever you are facing is a result of a grudge you are holding against your fellow man.
Grudge, pain of the past, unforgiveness - whether you are right or wrong .
please, put everything behind you; they are your adverts.
How will you be known, if people are not talking about you?
The same mouth will praise - the same mouth will condemn.
This mouth cannot say one thing; it will condemn and it will praise.
If you are expecting people to praise you, you should expect people to condemn you.
Whatever pain, whatever happened in the past, please put it behind you, move forward.
All these are adverts.
You will soon be known all over the world.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the name of Jesus!
Right now, put your demand on the anointing.
The right hand of God is power.
Let the power of God come down.
Let the power of the Lord come down
Let the power of the Lord from Heaven come down
You demon, in all places in your life,
begin to command them out, in the name of Jesus.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
You demon, listen to the voice of my people; I command you right now to leave my people!
I command you to leave my people!
Leave my people!
In the name of Jesus, leave my people!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus.
Look, there are many things we need to observe when we are praying.
When you pray, wait; you talk - let God talk.
You pause and wait; let God talk.
When you continue to pray, you are not allowing God to reply you.
We are not allowing God. When you are praying -
we are praying: "Leave my people, in Jesus' name, amen!" - you pause.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
You wait to see what God is about to do.
But we don't wait. Even in our home, we continue to pray, pray -
you are not waiting for God to talk to you.
You talk - God talks.
But it's one-sided - your prayer.
When you pray, I will join you in prayer. I say, "Ok, prayer", we pray.
When I now come in to say, "Hey, you demon, leave my people, in the name of Jesus!",
you say, "Amen!"; you pause.
You will see me pause. I will remain silent to see what God is about to do, how much God hears me.
But you will not wait to hear from God, you just... - your own is one way.
Just one way. If God talks, you don't want to listen. Your own is your own.
You have to pause. Can you see now?
It affects the response of God, if you don't allow Him to talk.
It really affects the response.
When you talk and you allow, you pause, wait to see -
while you are waiting, in your spirit you continue to say, "Thank You, God, for what You are about to do."
He manifests Himself.
But when you don't wait for Him to talk, to reply, to respond to what you are asking for
and you continue to talk, it affects Him; He will just, "Ok, continue talking.
When you get tired, you can go home".
If I'm talking to you, let me see your hand.
Viewers at home, viewers all over the world, I hope you understand what I am saying.
When you are praying on your own, after praying, you pause, you remain silent.
In your heart you say, "Thank You, Lord!" It means you are expecting Him to respond.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Assume you have been doing this, you would suddenly see yourself falling down.
If I am talking to mama now...
How are you, mum?
I am fine. Thanks.
If I say, "How are you?", you will say, "Fine."
But I'm not even waiting for her to respond.
How are you?
Oh my God.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Or I now say... It's God, I say, "Give me bread!"
If I say, "Give me bread", I will wait for you to give me.
But we don't wait, we say, "Give me bread".
This is crazy.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
God's response is very important.
It is because we don't trust ourselves, we see prayer as conventional, in a traditional way -
we just have to pray because we are asked to pray.
If you really know you are talking to somebody, you should expect that somebody to reply.
If you know you are talking to somebody, you should also pause for the response of that person.
But in this case, you don't even believe you are talking to somebody - that is why we talk, talk, talk.
We are talking to someone, somebody in the person of the Holy Ghost.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
God's response. Let someone say: "God's response."
I can't hear you.
[God's response.]
God's response must be noted.
When you say a word, you must wait for His response in the same moment.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Every antichrist in every place in your life, leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
The cause of nightmare in your business, in your health,
the cause of nightmare in your marriage, in your family,
the cause of nightmare in your finances, begin to rebuke them and command them out.
In the name of Jesus!
Every cause of nightmare - out!
Out!
Come on!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Those under the canopy, every demon - the cause of nightmare in your career,
the cause of nightmare in your business, in your family, in your marriage -
I command them out!
Out!
Prayer!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Vomiting Blood & Poisonous Substances
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I mean unpleasant situation - that is what I mean by nightmare.
The cause of nightmare in your marriage,
the cause of nightmare in your career,
the cause of nightmare in your business,
the cause of nightmare in your finances, in your business partner -
begin to rebuke them.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Those under the canopy, outside there, I say to you - every antichrist,
every pain in hidden places, I command them to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
You demon!
Prayer.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I said I am the spirit from the husband's family.
I destroy all her efforts, I see and I destroy. Her husband, poverty everywhere.
Viewers all over the world - East, South, West, North - wherever you are,
every cause of nightmare - I mean demon in every place in your life -
I command them to leave you, in the name of Jesus.
Leave my people!
Leave their marriage, leave their career, leave their business,
leave their career,
leave their finances,
leave their health, in the name of Jesus!
Rejoice.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
That disease, demon is behind it.
That infirmity, demon is responsible for it.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances In The Overflow Congregation
That sickness, demon knows about it.
You infirmity, leave my people!
You infirmity, I command you in the name of Jesus, leave my people!
Leave my people!
Demon and his infirmity, demon and his sickness, disease
in your bones, in your fluid, in your tendons,
I command them to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever you might have eaten on the table of your enemy, in the dream -
Be flushed out, in the name of Jesus!
Be it in your kidney, be flushed out, in the name of Jesus!
By the blood of Jesus, by the power of the Holy Ghost!
Holy Ghost!
Say - out!
In the name of Jesus!
Vomiting Blood & Poisonous Substances
Wherever disease, sickness, infirmity is located -
be it in your blood, in your kidneys, in your liver,
in your bones - begin to fetch them out by the blood of Jesus, the power of the Holy Ghost!
Holy Ghost!
Prayer.
Vomiting Blood & Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Who is number one?
Ancestral spirit.
Who is number two?
Python spirit.
How did you destroy him?
I have finished this guy. He is already gone. He has nothing.
Move like an ancient serpent.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Act like a serpent.
How did you destroy his business, his career?
We own his certificates.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
At the command of Jesus, I say - you infirmity, leave my people.
You sickness, leave my people!
You disease, leave my people. I say, leave my people.
Leave my people!
Open your lips. Anywhere the sickness is located - in your blood, in your fluid.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
In the mighty name of Jesus!
I say to your blood - every strange thing,
I say to your fluid - every strange thing,
I say to you liver - every strange thing,
I say to your kidney - every strange thing,
I say to your organs - be flushed out!
You disease, be flushed out! You sickness, be flushed out!
You infirmity, be flushed out by the blood of Jesus!
Begin to flush it out by the blood of Jesus!
Blood of Jesus! Power of Holy Ghost!
Holy Ghost!
Begin to flush it out.
Flush it out!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Blood & Poisonous Substances
You familiar spirit with all your sickness, with all your disease.
You familiar spirit, in the name of Jesus, I command you out with all your disease!
Out, with all your disease!
Prayer!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Blood & Poisonous Substances
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I want to destroy her!
What have you done to her marriage?
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Right now, you can pray for your nation.
Ask God for power over corruption, misrule, misappropriation and idolatry.
Prayer For The Nations
With Prophet T.B.Joshua
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
I cover your nation with the blood of Jesus.
Give thanks to Him. Hallelujah!
Begin to confess whom you are in Christ Jesus.
I'm healed; Jesus is my Healer. I'm delivered, Jesus is my Deliverer.
I'm redeemed; Jesus is my Redeemer. I'm saved; Jesus is my Saviour.
Confess your stand in Jesus Christ's name.
For those who are coming for the first time, your first appearance to Christ -
open your lips and say after me:
Lord Jesus, I am a sinner; come into my heart.
Wash me with Your precious blood; save my soul today.
Make me a channel of shining light where there is darkness.
Make me a channel of humility where there is pride.
Lord Jesus, make me a channel of pardon where there is injury.
Make me a channel of love where there is hatred. In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
In Jesus' name. Hallelujah!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
TT: Monica Asefa 24/01/19
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 30/01/2019 + Mel